&gt；&gt；steve kinney：所以当我们去
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: So when we go and
访问对象上的属性我们做这个称为动态查找的事情。
access a property on an object we do
this thing called Dynamic Lookup.
也就是说，好的，我不知道x是否在这个物体上。
Which is, okay,
I don't know if x is on this object.
我不知道它是不是在这个原型上，对吧？
I don't know if it's on this prototype,
right?
我不知道什么是。
I don't know what anything is.
我必须弄清楚所有这些东西。
I've gotta figure out all this stuff.
所以点火开始并读出。
And so the ignition goes and reads it.
点火解释器打开所有的说明书读数，
The ignition interpreter opens up
the spec reads through everything,
所有这些都能工作并试图找出答案，对吗？
does all this work and
tries to figure it out, right?
这样做很慢，对吧？
Doing that is slow, right?
而且计算机擅长做我们不想做的重复性工作，但是
And computers are good at doing repetitive
work that we don't wanna do but
他们也善于记住事情而不去做。
they're also good at remembering
things and not doing it.
再一次，你可以看到它的发展方向，
And again you can see where this is going,
做事情不比做事情快，对吧？
not doing stuff faster than doing stuff,
right?
所以V8所做的就是它保留了一个秘密类型的系统
So what V8 does is it keeps
a secret type system that it
不会在背后告诉你。
doesn't tell you about behind your back.
所以就像，听着，你之前问过我这个物体的x。
So it's like, listen, you asked me for
x on this object before.
我查过了。
I have looked it up.
我已经看过规则了。
I've read the rules.
我知道它在哪里。
I know where it is.
内存中有这么多位。
It's this many bits over in memory.
好吧，我不会再这么做了。
Fine, I'm not doing this again.
对，而且速度很快，也是非常危险的。
Right and that's fast,
it's also incredibly dangerous.
所有你看到的东西都像巨人
All of the things that you see like giant
系统架构被破坏，比如Spectrum。
system architectures being
compromised like Spectrum.
这就像当我们读取记忆时，我们不应该读取它，如果它是坏的，对吗？
It's like when we read memory we shouldn't
read from it's if it's bad right?
所以如果你搞错了，那可能是一场全面的崩溃，所以
So if you get that wrong that
could be a full crash, so
你可以猜到它在如何做到这一点上会非常保守，对吗？
you can guess that it's gonna be pretty
conservative in how it does that, right?
所以这就是为什么我们看到事情走上不同道路的原因。
So that's why we saw cases where
things went down different paths.
就像(笑)我来查，没事的。
It was like [LAUGH] I'll do the lookup,
it's fine.
但一切都是一样的，
But things where everything
was exactly the same,
就好像我知道这个东西。
it was like I know about this object.
我做过这件事。我读过规则手册
I've done this.
I've read the rulebook,
我以前见过这种物体。
I've seen this kind of object before.
我知道该怎么做，我会为你做得更快。
I know what to do,
I will do it faster for you.
所以让我们来看看一些东西。
So let's actually look at some stuff.
好的，所以每件事都有一个叫做Hidden Class的东西。
All right, so everything gets
this thing called a Hidden Class.
这就是它在Chrome中的名字，它在Firefox中被称为不同的东西，
That's what it's called in Chrome, it's
called something different in Firefox,
它在Safari中被称为不同的东西。
it's called something different in Safari.
我们现在要使用Hidden Class，因为为什么不使用。
We're going to use Hidden Class
right now because why not.
因为它是隐藏的，看起来像是一把小斗篷和一把匕首，谁不喜欢呢？
Because its hidden, it seems like a little
cloak and dagger, who doesn't like that?
好的，我们创建一个对象，它有一个隐藏的类，我们称它为C0。
All right, so we make an object, it's
got the hidden class, we'll call it C0.
它其实有个奇怪的长名字，我们不会用的。
It's actually got some weird long
name that we're not gonna use.
对吧？C0似乎对我们有好处。
RIght?
C0 seems good for us.
我们向其添加y属性。
We add a y property to it.
好的，现在这是一个不同的行动，就像它有一个不同的形状。
All right, now it's a different op,
like it's got a different shape to it.
对吧？
Right?
现在是C1。
It's now C1.
它经过了这条路。
And it went through this path.
你可以从C0转到C1，对吗？
You can go from C0 to C1, right?
但如果我们一开始就像它既有x又有
But if we started off
like it has both x and
Y，那是它自己的不同的隐藏类。
y, that's it's own different hidden class.
好像我们不知道似的。
Like we don't know.
秩序很重要。
The order matters.
属性添加到对象的顺序
The order in which the properties
got added to the object
当我们查查财产是什么的时候很重要。
matters when we look
up what a property is.
所以如果一个物体到达的路径
So if the path that an object
went down to get to
所具有的属性是不同的。
the properties that is has is different.
我们无法使用查找的缓存版本。
We can't use the cached
version of the lookup.
我们必须继续前进，每次都要经历这个过程。
We have to go ahead and
go through the process every time.
所以就像你只能在链条上前进，你不能，
So like you can only move forward
in the chain, you can not,
就像我们从C0到C1一样。
like we went from C0 to C1.
你不能从C1开始。
You can't start at C1.
如果你从C0开始
If you start at C0 and
你去C1，如果你从别的地方开始，你必须走你自己的路。
you go to C1, if you start off somewhere
else, you got to go down your own path.
你只能在这个链条上前进。
You can only move forward in this chain.
所以你有C0，我们有属性，变成C1。
So you have C0,
we have the property, becomes C1.
别理它。
Ignore that.
是的，修好下一张幻灯片。
Yeah, fix the next slide.
[笑]如果是同样的属性，那么我们直接去C2。
[LAUGH] If it's the same property
then we go directly to C2.
对，如果我们删除另一个属性，那么它就会变成自己的属性，而如果我们删除另一个属性
Right and if we delete another property
then that moves to it's own versus if we
从上面的对象中删除了相同的属性，这是一个不同的路径，对吗？
deleted that same property from the above
object that's a different path, right?
除非事物以同样的方式创造，
Unless things are created the same way,
他们走的是同一条路，VA不会试图想象他们是同一件事。
they go down the same path VA doesn't try
to imagine that they are the same thing.
所以当我们试图思考我们如何制造我们的物体时，这是很有用的
So that's useful when we try to think
about how we make our objects and
我们对我们的对象所做的。
what we do to our objects.
如果我们能让他们沿着同样的道路前进
If we can keep them going
along the same path and
我们以非常系统的方式做事。
we do things in a very systematic way.
所以当我们为
So when we make functions for
做事情VS函数每次都以相同的方式运行VS在这里
doing things vs the functions going to
run the same way every time vs here
我将以这种方式随意编写代码，而在这里我将以另一种方式来做。
I'm gonna willy-nilly code it this way and
here I'm gonna do it this other way.
你可以选择自己不参与其中的一些事情。
You can opt yourself out
of some of these things.
很酷，所以我们之前在一些代码中看到了它。
Cool, so we saw it with some code earlier.
还记得我是如何拥有那5000万美元，而它是另一种类型的吗？
Remember how I had that 50 million and
it was a different type?
那很奇怪对吧？
That was weird, right?
让我们实际谈谈它所经历的过程。
Let's actually talk about
the process that it goes through.
当对象从未被创建时，
When an object has never been created,
我们以前从未见过那处房产，在那里他们都在工作
we've never seen that property before,
where it both works for
推测性优化以及这些隐藏类。
the speculative optimization as
well as these hidden classes.
就像，我们不知道x是什么，我以前从未见过它。
It's like, we don't know what x is,
I've never seen it before.
就像薛定谔的类型。
It's like Schroedinger's type.
没有，因为我们从未见过它，也没有任何信息。
It's None, because we've never seen it and
we have no information.
当我们第一次看到它时，我们要么看到它是一个数字。
The first time we see it,
we either see that it's a number.
这要么是一个很长的数字，要么就是我们所说的SignedSmall，
Which is either a really long number,
or what we call a SignedSmall,
一个很小的数字，或者是一个字符串或者这个叫做BigInt的东西。
a small number, or it's a string or
this thing called a BigInt.
这是第二阶段的提案
Which is a stage two proposal for
实际上拥有在JavaScript中有意义的大数字。
actually having large numbers
that make sense in JavaScript.
想象一下现在还不存在。
Just imagine that one doesn't exist for
now.
所以一旦你成为一个分配给小的数字或者
And so once you become either
a number assigned small or
字符串在推测性优化中，很酷。
string in that speculative optimization,
cool.
只能在此晶格上向前移动。
You can only move forward on this lattice.
数字或古怪基本上就是，你知道那些事情，
Number or oddball is basically,
you know those things,
你有没有读过那些博客帖子，他们就像是，
you ever read those blog posts and
they're like,
JavaScript搞砸了，因为true加上true等于2。
JavaScript's messed up because
true plus true equals two.
因为TRUE在技术上是1，而FALSE在技术上是0，RIGHT和
Right cuz true is technically 1 and
false is technically 0, right and
所有那种僵硬的权利。
all that kind of stiff right.
如果我们第二次看到数字1和true，它是一个数字或
If we saw the number one and
true a second time, it's a number or
这是一个没有定义的奇怪的东西，所有这些最终都是一样的东西。
it's an oddball no undefined, any of these
all end up being kind of same thing.
所以，是的，我们看到每一种都在适当的位置。
So yeah we see each of
those kind of in place.
但如果你看到一次数字和第二次看到的字符串，
But if you saw the number once and
a string the second time,
那我们就不知道发生了什么
then we don't know what's going on.
什么都行。
It's any.
我们不能，在这一点上，我们要么更接近多态，要么
We can't, at this point, we get
either closer to that polymorphism or
变质作用对吧？
metamorphism, right?
我们不能跟踪这些东西是什么，对吧？
We can't keep track of what
these things are, right?
所以事情就像是经过了这个过程。
So things kind of like
move through this process.